If he is determined to protect Fang Yongping,
如果他下定决心要保护方永平，
It's hard for us
对我们来说很难
in his body.
在他的身体里。
That's it.
就是这样。
Cara Fang Yongping
Cara Fang Yongping
Solve all problems in one click.
一击解决所有问题。
Provincial Commission for Discipline Inspection Investigation Team
省纪委调查组
Participated in the investigation.
已参与调查。
Will not let Fang Yongping
不会让方永平
Letting go so easily.
如此轻易地放手。
What if Zheng Guoxian survives?
如果郑国贤活下来怎么办？
it depends
这取决于
How much evidence was collected.
收集了多少证据。
But there are two people.
但有两个人。
We can pay attention to it.
我们可以关注一下。
Chen Ting dan Fang Lu.
Chen Ting dan Fang Lu.
We are watching Chen Ting.
我们在看陈婷。
We found out that he was related to Fang Yongping.
我们发现他和方永平有关系。
Before Zheng Guoxian was investigated,
在郑国贤被调查之前，
They are still on the mountain.
他们还在山上。
On the top of the mountain.
在山顶上。
Her relationship with Fang Yongping
她与方永平的关系
Zheng Guoxian pasti tahu.
Zheng Guoxian pasti tahu.
But so far,
但到目前为止，
[Zheng Guoxian]
[郑国贤]
He was not involved.
他没有参与。
This shows that he is deliberately protecting her.
这说明他是故意保护她的。
Chen Ting is this example.
陈婷就是这个例子。
in this case.
在这种情况下。
but we had fun
但我们玩得很开心
There is no evidence for him.
没有他的证据。
Di mana Fang Lu?
Di mana Fang Lu?
How about it
怎么样
How are they going?
他们进展如何？
We doubt
我们怀疑
Fang Lu was imprisoned abroad
方璐在国外入狱
Maybe there is a reason.
也许有一个原因。
But Fang Lu himself
但方禄本人
no doubt.
毫无疑问。
Fang Lu is very likely
方璐很可能
Move Fang Yongping’s pillar.
搬动方永平的支柱。
of.
的。
Fang Luyou
方璐有
Also a gamer.
也是一名游戏玩家。
This shows that he is very curious
这说明他很好奇
Adversarial agent games.
对抗代理博弈。
You want to take advantage of Fang Lu's curiosity
你想利用方璐的好奇心
How is your relationship with Fang Lu?
你和方璐关系怎么样？
I think Fang Lu
我觉得方璐
Pretty good.
相当不错。
Which one is better
哪一款好
very sincere
非常真诚
Not used to it
不习惯
less urban
不那么都市
Basically it can be ruled out
基本上可以排除
Maybe he's a spy.
也许他是一名间谍。
Your decision is only a reference.
你的决定只是一个参考。
do not forget,
不要忘记，
He was once one of them
他也曾经是其中一员
game player
游戏玩家
This is also right
这也是对的
People who can play offline missions
可以玩离线任务的人
Even the IQ is not too bad
就连智商也不会太差
he is
他是
Graduate students from internationally renowned high schools.
国际知名高中的研究生。
Stopped?
停了？
Do you have any opinion?
你有什么意见？
He is a better agent than you
他是比你更好的经纪人
what do you mean
你是什​​么意思
Didn't he find something wrong with the game?
他没发现游戏有问题吗
Remind Yaoyao to quit
提醒瑶瑶退出
of.
的。
if
如果
He understands the people around him
他了解他周围的人
because of the game
由于游戏的原因
【Because of the game. 】
【因为游戏。】
what happens?
会发生什么？
And you?
你呢？
If I,
如果我，
I will definitely investigate the truth.
我一定会调查真相。
I think he is the same.
我想他也是一样的。
You kill with a knife.
你用刀杀人。
You changed the word.
你改变了这个词。
I'm called to use energy
我被称为使用能量
Awesome, Sister Xi
厉害了夕姐
Come up with a plan and tell me.
想一个计划并告诉我。
no problem.
没问题。
I am better than you.
我比你好。
sneaky trick
鬼祟的伎俩
rogue operation
流氓操作
And one more thing.
还有一件事。
i need to remind you
我需要提醒你
Yaoyao logs into the game again
瑶瑶再次登录游戏
Did he go to see Boss Zhang?
他去见张老板了吗？
I guess he didn't tell you.
我猜他没有告诉你。
No.
不。
Be careful.
当心。
OK
好的。
Some artists invited today
今天邀请的一些艺术家
Although he is not very old,
虽然年纪不大，
But their works are abroad
但他们的作品在国外
foreign.
国外。
and got a good response.
并得到了良好的反响。
Next is their job
接下来是他们的工作
Will be exhibited at Cloud Art Museum.
将在云端美术馆展出。
Next, let's go
接下来，我们走吧
Be aware of the big screen.
要注意大屏幕。
to understand
去理解
Works by several artists
几位艺术家的作品
Not many people came today.
今天来的人不多。
especially today
尤其是今天
Invite some of these artists
邀请其中一些艺术家
quite common
相当常见
not many people know
没有多少人知道
most of them
他们中的大多数
It's a free ticket.
是免费门票。
this young man
这个年轻人
Need to be seen by others.
需要被别人看到。
slowly.
慢慢地。
OK
好的。
you go first.
你先走。
I listened for a while
我听了一会儿
OK
好的
Author: Pang Yun
作者：庞云
This is an abstract painting
这是一幅抽象画
It creates art.
它创造艺术。
Newly developed.
新开发的。
The first author is Wang Zhixin.
第一作者为王志新。
We see two paintings at the back
我们看到后面有两幅画
Chen Yuanlong did it
陈元龙做到了
This is a deep picture
这是一张深图
why are you here
你为什么在这
We'll meet again.
我们再见面。
When I came last time,
上次来的时候，
Don’t you have a free ticket?
没有一张免费票吗
So come and take a look.
所以来看看吧。
You seem to care a little
你好像有点在乎
This is my little gallery
这是我的小画廊
I think it's well done.
我认为做得很好。
Yes?
是的？
Now people like you
现在像你这样的人
not many people
没有很多人
not much.
不多。
Must support.
必须支持。
Actually, not Fucick.
事实上，不是福西克。
they are my friends.
他们是我的朋友。
Isn't it?
不是吗？
Graduated from Art Center
毕业于艺术中心
of.
的。
In fact, I've seen it before.
事实上，我以前见过。
their job
他们的工作
Deep impression.
深刻影响。
you are indeed
你确实是
Very concerned about modern art
非常关注现代艺术
Didn't expect that
没想到如此
something we all like
我们都喜欢的东西
very similar.
非常相似。
Will you be free tonight?
你今晚有空吗？
If you have time, go out for a drink.
如果有时间，可以出去喝一杯。
Let's drink.
我们喝吧。
I went in and listened again.
我进去又听了一遍。
here
这里
Sit here.
在这里坐。
Jamie.
杰米。
Mr. Fang.
方先生。
A gorgeous golden wine.
一款绚丽的金色葡萄酒。
Martini.
马提尼。
You drink that wine
你喝那酒
Tasteful
有品味
Didn't expect that
没想到如此
Not only do we have the same taste
我们不仅口味相同
And it tastes the same
而且味道也一样
Yaoyao never told me.
瑶瑶从来没有告诉过我。
Di Jinhai,
Di Jinhai,
With an old friend like you,
有你这样的老朋友，
maybe because
也许是因为
Our relationship is normal.
我们的关系很正常。
Incorrect
不正确
the relationship between you two
你们两个之间的关系
So amazing
太奇妙了
How to say
怎么说
Have you all experienced this?
你们都经历过吗
In the U.S?
在美国？
you misunderstood.
你误会了。
At that time we both
当时我们俩
Our relationship is very good.
我们的关系很好。
But after
但是之后
Thanks.
谢谢。
what should i say
我该怎么说
normal relationship
关系正常
I'm not asking about your relationship.
我不是在问你们的关系。
I mean,
我是说，
Have you experienced anything?
你经历过什么吗？
brother
兄弟
What do you want to ask?
你想问什么？
Yaoyao told me
瑶瑶告诉我了
Yaoyao has already told me
瑶瑶已经告诉我了
So come and confirm with me
所以你来跟我确认一下
Not considered recognition
不算认可
I believe what Yao Ming says
我相信姚明的话
after that
在那之后
you know
你知道
Yaoyao is injured
瑶瑶受伤了
because of the game
因为游戏
In fact, after that incident,
其实在那次事件之后，
I feel guilty.
我感到内疚。
I was serious
我是认真的
seriously.
严重地。
But he told me clearly
但他明确告诉我
He doesn't need my help
他不需要我的帮助
He has paid off all his debts.
他已经还清了所有的债务。
and
和
He doesn't play games anymore
他不再玩游戏了
You would never think
你绝对不会想到
There may be something wrong with this game
这游戏可能有问题
I'm a gamer too
我也是游戏玩家
What do you want to say?
你想说什么？
I guess
我猜测
The man behind this game
这个游戏的幕后主使
It's a spy organization.
是一个间谍组织。
Who are you
你是
Have you watched too many foreign movies?
国外电影看多了？
this thing
这东西
with me
与我一起
you two
你们俩
Why
为什么
No reason?
没有原因？
what do you have?
你有什么？
A special one?
特殊的一个？
you mean,
你的意思是，
My family background?
我的家庭背景？
certainly.
当然。
they are impossible
他们是不可能的
It’s for Yaoyao
是为了瑶瑶
But Yaoyao has
但瑶瑶却有
because of this
因为这
Not out yet
到现在还没出来
And you?
你呢？
Already retreated.
已经撤退了。
Do you think it is reasonable?
你觉得合理吗？
What clue are you trying to give me?
你想给我什么线索？
I won't give you directions.
我不会给你指路。
I just want to remind you.
我只是想提醒你。
This is my mobile phone number.
这是我的手机号。
If you need help,
如果你需要帮助，
contact me anytime
随时联系我
Why are you so interested?
你为什么这么感兴趣？
My stuff?
我的东西？
because of my father
因为我的父亲
He is the leader of Jinhai Biological Company.
是金海生物公司的领导者。
i face
我面对
Have the same problem as you.
和你有同样的问题。
Why are you so generous today?
你今天怎么这么大方？
Please make me a spa.
请给我做一个水疗中心。
there is nothing.
没有什么。
it costs some money
这要花一些钱
can only feel
只能感觉
True happiness?
真正的幸福？
Yes.
是的。
If so, this joy
如果是的话，这份喜悦
more.
更多的。
You are beautiful.
你很漂亮。
How are you and that guy?
你和那个家伙怎么样？
there is nothing.
没有什么。
Pretty good.
相当不错。
you tell me
你告诉我
how?
如何？
I noticed him flirting with other people
我注意到他和其他人调情
why this person
为什么这个人
So good at causing trouble
这么善于制造麻烦
Did you see him with that girl?
你看到他和那个女孩在一起了吗？
Which girl?
哪个女孩？
he teases the guy
他戏弄那个家伙
He is a man.
他是一个男人。
Why are there such people?
为什么会有这样的人呢？
Look how serious you are
看你多认真
I'm just kidding.
我只是在开玩笑。
I hope
我希望
No more secrets.
不再有秘密。
Oh yes.
哦是的。
I took two days off.
我请了两天假。
Lend me your car.
把你的车借给我吧。
Take my advice.
听听我的建议。
Some things cannot be forced.
有些事情是不能强求的。
There are many men.
有很多男人。
Throw it away.
把它扔掉吧。
Don't worry
不用担心
I know.
我知道。
Enter.
进入。
Lu.
鲁。
sister in law
嫂子
Where is Brother Zheng?
郑哥在哪里
I called him yesterday
昨天我给他打电话
hang up the phone
挂断电话
Come first.
先进来吧。
He was investigated.
他被调查了。
People from the National Security Bureau came this morning.
今天早上国安的人来了。
He asked me a lot of questions.
他问了我很多问题。
and left him at home.
并把他留在家里。
He took away all the materials and computers.
他拿走了所有的资料和电脑。
Orangukian.
奥兰古克安.
Did you tell me the reason?
有说一下原因吗？
I have no idea.
我不知道。
What is he doing?
他在做什么？
He told me nothing.
他什么也没告诉我。
Does my father know about this?
我父亲知道这件事吗？
I called Mayor Fang
我打电话给方市长
To Mayor Fang.
给方市长。
But no one answered.
但没有人回答。
Lu.
鲁。
please
请
Tell Mayor Fang.
告诉方市长。
Ever since Guoxian followed him,
自从国贤跟着他之后，
Saved him for many years.
救了他很多年。
Our children are still young.
我们的孩子还小。
We can't lose Dad.
我们不能失去爸爸。
Sister-in-law, don’t worry.
嫂子，别担心。
I will definitely investigate
我一定会调查
The matter was made clear.
这件事说清楚了。
Why are you so interested?
你为什么这么感兴趣？
My stuff?
我的东西？
because of my father
因为我的父亲
He is the leader of Jinhai Biological Company.
是金海生物公司的领导者。
i face
我面对
Have the same problem as you.
和你有同样的问题。
Why did you let me go?
你为什么让我走？
from now on,
今后，
Don't go anywhere.
别去任何地方。
Duduk di Jinhai.
Duduk di Jinhai.
I haven't finished studying yet
我还没学完呢
What can you do in Gimhae?
去金海可以玩什么？
I haven't finished reading the book yet.
书还没读完。
You can continue reading in Jinhai.
您可以在金海继续阅读。
Work can be arranged if you wish.
如果你愿意的话可以安排工作。
In short, there is only one condition.
简而言之，只有一个条件。
Don't leave my sight.
不要离开我的视线。
Don't take it out of your sight.
不要离开你的视线。
am i your dog
我是你的狗吗
Or your pet?
或者你的宠物？
why my life
为什么我的一生
I will follow you.
我会跟随你。
I am your father.
我是你爸爸。
I am the most responsible person
我是最有责任的人
In this world.
在这世上。
do you have
你有没有
As a father's responsibility?
作为父亲的责任？
Since childhood I
从小我就
How many days have you been with me?
你和我在一起多少天了？
How many times have you played with me?
你陪我玩了多少次？
i am indeed
我确实是
I owe you a lot.
我欠你很多。
But in this position
但在这个位置上
i'm not there
我不在那儿
time and effort
时间和精力
Take care of your family.
照顾家人。
OK
好的。
Don't accept a job
不要接受工作
Related to work matters.
与工作事务有关。
Let me ask you.
让我问问你。
what happen
发生什么事
what happen?
发生什么事？
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
you and my mother
你和我妈妈
We haven’t been together for a long time.
好久没在一起了。
Still hiding.
还躲着呢。
Don't let outsiders know
不要让外人知道
Because I'm afraid of you two
因为害怕你们两个
will affect you.
会影响你。
Deputy mayor position?
副市长的职位？
Dengar sini, Fang Yongping.
Dengar sini, Fang Yongping.
in your heart,
在你心里，
in your heart.
在你心里。
Talk again.
再说话。
I say in your heart
我在你心里说
in your heart.
在你心里。
You are very conceited.
你很自负。
listen.
听。
you...
你...
it's that person
是那个人
Come accuse me.
来指责我。
if i wasn't the mayor
如果我不是市长
do you remember today
你记得今天
Can you come back alive today?
今天能活着回来吗？
OK
好的。
from now on,
今后，
I won't ask you for a penny.
我不会向你要一分钱。
I'll prove it to you.
我会向你证明这一点。
This town is without you,
这个小镇没有你，
Will I starve to death?
我会饿死吗
Hello?
你好？
What are your plans tonight?
今晚你有什么计划？
I have a date with a friend.
我和一个朋友有个约会。
I can't accompany you anymore
我不能再陪你了
We will contact you later.
我们稍后会联系。
OK, call me later.
好的，稍后给我打电话。
National Security Agency
国家安全局
The investigation into Brother Zheng has already begun.
已经开始调查郑哥了。
Is the National Security Bureau looking for you?
国安局找你吗？
No.
不。
Wait for the National Security Agency to come find you.
等国安局来找你。
It's too late.
为时已晚。
really weird.
真奇怪。
After something happens,
有事发生后，
This spy is not looking for you.
这个间谍不是在找你。
what happen?
发生什么事？
I know this is hard to deal with.
我知道这很难处理。
I also tried to escape.
我也曾试图逃跑。
But it didn't work.
但没用。
own problem
自己的问题
Need to solve it yourself.
需要自己解决。
key
钥匙
Where should I start investigating?
我应该从哪里开始调查？
Try to think about it.
尝试思考一下。
In the past two years,
这两年，
Anyone
有没有人
Frequently contact Mayor Fang
经常联系方市长
his business
他的事
About him.
关于他。
Yaoyaoqie
瑶瑶切
Your bail was high at the time.
当时你的保释金很高
Therefore, he owes too much.
所以，他欠的太多了。
You are also looking for a lawyer.
您也在寻找律师。
That's right, it's Brother Zheng
没错，就是郑哥
If you have any friends, please find them
有朋友请找
What friend
什么朋友
I recommend you
我推荐你
Investigate spies
调查间谍
Have you contacted Mayor Fang?
你联系方市长了吗？
I learned programming.
我学了编程。
if you want to solve
如果你想解决的话
Simple procedure
程序简单
or email password.
或电子邮件密码。
I can help you.
我可以帮你。
certainly.
当然。
You can also do nothing.
你也可以什么都不做。
Wait for the National Security Agency to come find you.
等国安局来找你。
Chris Chen.
克里斯·陈.
Chen Ting.
Chen Ting.
There is a program code in the USB.
USB 中有一个程序代码。
Enter it into your computer
将其输入电脑中
Then it can be translated automatically
然后可以自动翻译
Simple password.
简单的密码。
how?
如何？
Did you discover anything?
你有发现什么吗？
not sure yet.
尚未确定。
It's about spies.
这与间谍有关。
but indeed
但确实
Some people are involved.
涉及到一些人。
Can you
你可以吗
Can you please keep it a secret first?
请先保密好吗？
sure.
当然可以。
what else?
还有什么？
Need my help?
需要我的帮助吗？
Not yet.
暂时没有。
there are some things
有一些事情
I wanted to investigate myself.
我想调查一下我自己。
If you need help,
如果你需要帮助，
Please feel free to let me know.
请随时告诉我。
Thanks.
谢谢。
You're welcome
不客气
Did you find anything?
有什么发现吗？
Fang Yongping always uses
方永平总是用
Fang Lu overseas account
方璐海外账号
There’s also a guy named Chris Chen
还有一个叫克里斯​​·陈的人
His name is Chris Chen.
他的名字叫克里斯·陈。
According to your instructions,
根据您的指示，
Contents of USB
USB 中的内容
I've arrived here.
我已经到了这里。
Go back and see for yourself
你自己回去看看吧
The greatest agents really stand out
最伟大的特工确实与众不同
It's just normal
正常而已
What's his plan after this?
这之后他有什么计划呢？
He wasn't sure about the information yet.
他对这个信息还不确定。
It must have something to do with spies.
一定和间谍有关系。
Therefore, he had to continue investigating.
所以，他还得继续调查。
Okay, let's go with him.
好吧，我们就和他一起去吧
Don't be too aggressive.
不要太激进。
waiting time.
等待时间。
understand.
理解。
Is anyone following you today?
今天有人关注你吗？
impossible.
不可能的。
Don't look back.
别回头。
There is a car behind.
后面有一辆车。
He was busy following us.
他正忙着跟着我们。
Is he a spy?
他是间谍吗？
I have no idea.
我不知道。
if they find out
如果他们发现
You have a relationship with Fang Lu,
你和方璐有关系，
You will run into problems.
你会遇到问题。
how is it like?
什么样的？
You go back first.
你先回去吧。
Wait for me to investigate
等我去调查
Who is the person behind it.
背后的人是谁。
let me tell you.
让我告诉你。
OK
好的
Tian Yang
田阳
You check the license plate number.
你检查一下车牌号。
IDE0513。
IDE0513。
It’s fun to follow Huang Zicheng in this car.
这车跟着黄子诚挺好玩的。
The owner of this train is named Zhou Siqi.
这列火车的主人名叫周思琪。
Jae-cheol is studying.
宰哲正在读书。
philosophy
哲学
Yao Yao.
Yao Yao.
this is an investment
这是一项投资
Domestic and overseas.
国内外。
Boss, Mr. Fang is here.
老板，方先生来了。
We'll talk again later.
我们过一会再聊。
Why?
为什么？
elder sister.
姐姐。
Something happened in our family
我们家发生了一些事情
Brother Zheng was taken away by the Discipline Inspection Commission
郑哥被纪委带走
The National Security Bureau also came to investigate
国安也前来调查
Sit down and talk.
坐下来谈谈。
OK
好的。
Why involve Guo An?
为什么要牵涉到郭安呢？
I guess
我猜测
It has to do with things in the United States.
和美国的事情有关。
you mean,
你的意思是，
In the U.S?
在美国？
of.
的。
Oh, how about it.
噢，怎么样。
done before
以前做过
you are looking for me
你在找我
that's right.
这是正确的。
why it is related to
为什么它与
With that thing?
与那个东西？
I guess
我猜测
Some people deliberately persecute us.
有些人故意迫害我们。
Who wants to abuse you?
谁想虐待你？
Spy group.
间谍团。
who told you that?
谁告诉你？
Brother Zheng once advised me
郑兄曾经劝过我
Don't let me play games
不让我玩游戏
at last,
最后，
I have withdrawn from the national security case
我已经退出国安案了
I think
我觉得
The two must be related.
两者必须相关。
So why a spy?
那么，为什么是间谍
Why did he abuse you?
他为什么虐待你？
I have no idea.
我不知道。
I guess he came to see my dad.
我猜他是来找我爸爸的。
What's your plan?
你的计划是什么？
how?
如何？
There are no plans yet.
目前还没有计划。
Have you asked Mayor Fang?
你问过方市长了吗？
I do not know how to put it.
我不知道该怎么说。
elder sister.
姐姐。
what should I do
我应该怎么办
what should I do?
我应该怎么办？
this matter
这件事
Regarding this matter.
关于这件事。
You calm down first.
你先冷静一下。
and discussed with Mayor Fang.
并与方市长进行了讨论。
Now
现在
Isn't he very good?
他不是很好吗？
maybe this thing
也许这个东西
Not as serious as you think.
没有你想象的那么严重。
anything,
任何事物，
you can come and see me
你可以来看我
I will definitely try my best to help you.
我一定会尽力帮助你。
Thank you, brother.
谢谢兄弟。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Hari ini, Chen Ting dan Fang Yongping
Hari ini, Chen Ting dan Fang Yongping
Meet again in Nanshan Villa Area.
再次相约南山别墅区。
In addition, we also found Fang Lu
另外，我们还找到了方璐
Also secretly followed Chen Ting.
也偷偷跟着陈婷。
OK
好的。
Why don't you eat? wait for me.
你为什么不吃？你等我。
where did you go?
你去哪儿？
I went to visit a friend.
我去看望一个朋友。
What friend
什么朋友
that's right
这是正确的
Do not lie to me.
不要骗我。
Fang Lu.
Fang Lu.
Why are you looking for Fang Lu?
你为什么要找方璐？
I'm investigating him.
我正在调查他。
Didn't I tell you?
我没告诉过你吗？
It is very dangerous to associate with him.
和他交往是非常危险的。
Are you hiding anything from me?
你有瞒着我吗？
do what?
做什么？
I'd like to reply.
我想回复一下。
Fight back!
反击！
Fang Lu.
Fang Lu.
It's not that easy.
其实没那么容易。
he looks
他看上去
no problem.
没问题。
but his father
但他的父亲
like there's a problem
就像有问题一样
you mean,
你的意思是，
Are you two investigating Mayor Fang?
你们两个在调查方市长？
I guess
我猜测
Spies used him
间谍利用他
Threatening Mayor Fang.
威胁方市长。
Secretary to Mayor Fang
方市长秘书
Arrested by the National Security Agency.
被国家安全局逮捕。
The National Security Agency got involved.
国家安全局介入。
Does he understand you?
他了解你吗？
have no idea
不知道
Zicheng, listen to me.
子成，你听我说。
No matter the spy
不管间谍
Or the National Security Agency.
或国家安全局。
They know you helped Fang Lu.
他们知道你帮助了方璐。
There will definitely be problems.
肯定会有问题。
I know.
我知道。
I know this is very dangerous.
我知道这非常危险。
So I don't allow you to join
所以我不允许你加入
Task assigned by Boss Zhang
张老板交给的任务
It's to protect you.
是为了守护你。
Have you reported to Boss Zhang?
你向张老板汇报了吗？
No.
不。
but he already knows
但他已经知道了
We met Fang Lu.
我们见到了方璐。
Sorry to bother you.
抱歉打扰您了。
I'm not afraid of problems.
我不怕出现问题。
But you have to tell me.
但你必须告诉我。
we all can
我们都可以
find a way to deal with them
找到对付他们的方法
correct
正确的
of.
的。
sorry.
对不起。
I shouldn't have kept secrets from you.
我不应该对你保密。
Next,
下一个，
What's your plan?
你的计划是什么？
Master the secrets of Night Mist.
掌握夜雾的秘密。
Fight them.
与他们战斗。
Don't you use eggs to hit stones?
你不是用鸡蛋去打石头吗？
I know I can't fight him.
我知道我斗不过他。
but my hands
但我的双手
At least have some chips, right?
至少有一些筹码吧？
if you can't hide
如果你无法隐藏的话
I can also surrender to the National Security Bureau.
我还可以去国安局自首。
to reduce the penalty.
以减轻处罚。
Now for us,
现在对我们来说，
the most important
最重要的
It's to save yourself.
是为了拯救自己。
Fang Lu has been looking for me.
方璐一直在找我。
He already suspected
他已经怀疑
American things
美国的事
Related to spies.
与间谍有关。
How does he know?
他怎么知道？
He said
他说
Zheng Guoxian reminded.
郑国贤提醒道。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
Judging from his tone,
从他的语气来看，
he is still there
他还在
On a speculative level.
在猜测层面。
Don't know what happened inside.
不知道里面发生了什么。
He will definitely ask carefully.
他一定会仔细询问的。
You can't put this thing away
这东西不能放
Act arbitrarily.
任意妄为。
if not
如果不
find a way
找到方法
Stay away from this.
远离这个。
And temporarily left Jinhai.
并暂时离开金海。
He won't agree to it.
他不会同意的。
our company
我们公司
The project will be developed in France.
将在法国开发该项目。
in the art gallery,
在美术馆里，
We are still negotiating cooperation with the Olympic Games.
还在与奥运会洽谈合作。
this matter
这件事
I've told him this before.
我之前已经告诉过他了。
I'll go with him too.
我也会和他一起去。
after finishing
完成后
Something here,
这里的东西，
I will go back with him.
我会和他一起回去。
This is a strategy.
这是一种策略。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Are you sure it's Yao Ming?
你确定是姚明？
Didn't betray Huang Zicheng
没有背叛黄子成
I do not think so.
我不这么认为。
If he betrayed Huang Zicheng,
如果他背叛了黄子成，
He doesn't have to
他不必
di hadapan Huang Zicheng,
di hadapan Huang Zicheng,
di hadapan Huang Zicheng.
di hadapan Huang Zicheng.
Yes
是的
You can fight Babali
可以和八八里战斗
dengan Huang Zicheng?
dengan Huang Zicheng?
who knows.
谁知道。
But everyone has a desire to live
但每个人都有一个活下去的愿望
The same goes for Yaoyao
瑶瑶也是一样
if you can give it to him
如果你可以给他
There is a chance to go ashore,
有机会上岸，
I believe he will be willing
我相信他会愿意
Yao Yao dan Huang Zicheng
Yao Yao dan Huang Zicheng
dengan Huang Zicheng
dengan Huang Zicheng
For his evaluation
对于他的评价
Need to be more careful.
需要更加小心。
understand.
理解。
Where is Fang Lu?
方璐呢？
Fang Lu already knew
方璐已经知道了
Hubungan Fang Yongping dan Chen Ting.
hubungan Fang Yongping dan Chen Ting.
it depends
这取决于
Fang Yongping.
Fang Yongping.
Where have you been so late?
这么晚了你去哪儿了？
Work content
工作内容
Delayed.
延迟了。
Working with women.
与女性一起工作。
I didn't expect it was you and Chen Ting
我没想到是你和陈婷
So tight.
这么紧。
are you talking?
你在说话吗？
How to transfer money?
如何转账？
how do you know?
你怎么知道？
Under my nose,
在我的眼皮底下，
in front of me.
在我眼前。
How disgusting.
真恶心。
It seems I need
看来我需要
I need to talk to you seriously
需要认真地跟你谈谈
Is there anything else to discuss?
还有什么要讨论的吗？
With the help of my lover,
在爱人的帮助下，
With the help of your loved one.
在你爱人的帮助下。
Finally, I remember
最后，我记得
I have to rely on my own efforts
我要靠自己的努力
Use your own efforts.
用自己的努力。
I'm really funny.
我真的很有趣。
in your eyes
在你眼里
am i
我是吗
who can't get help
谁无法得到帮助
No.
不。
The results show
结果表明
the decision you make now
你现在做出的决定
It all depends on your own efforts
这一切都取决于你自己的努力
Use your own efforts.
用自己的努力。
I know
我知道
I know.
我知道。
I'm tired
我累了
What kind of person is my father?
我的父亲是一个什么样的人？
I didn't find out until today
直到今天我才发现
you more
你更
You're not even smart.
你甚至都不聪明。
After the incident in the United States,
美国事件之后，
Are there spies looking for you?
有间谍在找你吗？
of.
的。
After hearing the news
得知消息后
In the U.S,
在美国，
Your mother and I are both worried.
我和你妈妈都很担心。
We started looking for a lawyer.
我们开始寻找律师。
Find a way.
寻找方法。
That day,
那天，
i received a letter
我收到一封信
Weird email.
奇怪的电子邮件。
this matter
这件事
just me
只有我
Secretary Jung knew.
荣格秘书知道。
I have no idea
我不知道
Got the news.
得到这个消息。
what is the background
背景是什么
how?
如何？
This is manageable.
这是可以管理的。
Lawyer's unrelated business
律师的不相关业务
We've already discussed it.
我们已经讨论过了。
I can fly to the United States this weekend.
这个周末可以飞往美国。
Lu Jiamin
卢嘉敏
Details till there
详细情况直到那里
and make it more detailed.
并使其更加详细。
Thanks
谢谢
where to.
去那里。
at this time,
此时，
I can't go out
我无法出去
I see.
我明白。
I can
我会
Safety.
安全。
more
多一点
this matter
这件事
Don't worry.
不用担心。
No one else will know.
不会被别人知道。
who knows?
谁知道？
one night,
一夜，
that person
那个人
Came here suddenly.
突然来到这里。
Tuan Fang.
Tuan Fang.
Hello.
你好。
Who are you?
你是谁？
Someone can help you.
有人可以帮助你。
You sent an email
您发送了电子邮件
Have you posted it?
你发好了吗？
my child.
我的孩子。
I will find a way to save him.
我会想办法救他的。
I don't need your help.
我不需要你的帮助。
so you...
那么你...
Why don't you?
你为什么不呢？
To protect your child?
为了保护你的孩子？
I heard
我听说
The mayor will
市长将
Serve as deputy mayor.
担任副市长。
Congratulations.
恭喜。
Dan Fang Lu
但方璐
at this critical moment.
在这个关键时刻。
Have a headache?
头疼吧？
It seems you know a lot.
看来你懂得很多啊。
I have no idea.
我不知道。
I will not bother you.
我不会打扰你。
The son of the district chairman.
地区主席的儿子。
Go to the United States to study.
去美国留学。
Concealed personal pistol, arrested.
藏匿私人手枪，被捕。
this keyword
这个关键字
If disclosed,
如果披露，
I'm afraid
我耽心
against you
针对你
I know you
我认识你
You have worked hard during this time.
这段时间你们辛苦了。
I hope my wish can come true
希望能够实现自己的愿望
at this time,
此时，
at this time
此时
so terrible.
太糟糕了。
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Do you want to threaten me?
你想威胁我吗？
This is not a threat.
这不是威胁。
This is an opportunity.
这是一个机会。
I hope we all
我希望我们都是
use this opportunity
借此机会
Cooperate with each other.
互相合作。
So, do you agree with them?
那么，你同意他们的观点吗？
then,
当时，
if i don't agree
如果我不同意的话
they will let you
他们会让你
go to jail.
进监狱。
I was slandered right then and there.
我当时就被诽谤了。
then,
当时，
We need a lawyer.
我们需要一名律师。
Where is dad?
爸爸呢？
You always worry about this case
你总是担心这个案子
It will affect your promotion.
会影响你的晋升。
So, you prefer to be a spy.
所以，你更愿意当间谍。
It's not as easy as you think.
这并不像你想象的那么容易。
what you think
你认为呢
Why Chen Ting?
为什么是陈婷？
We have hired a lawyer
我们已经聘请了律师
China's.
中国的。
But after the demise of mankind,
但人类灭亡后，
Under the obstruction of the spy organization,
在间谍组织的阻挠下，
never
决不
come to save you
来拯救你
Chen Ting.
Chen Ting.
American local lawyer.
美国当地律师。
What's up with her?
她怎么了？
Isn't it someone else?
不是别人吗？
Is he a spy?
他是间谍吗？
Now, a spy organization
现在，一个间谍组织
Contact me through him.
通过他与我联系。
Yeah.
呀呀。
are you old
你老了吗
He is looking for you and you only care about him.
他在找你，你只关心他。
If I knew this would happen
如果我知道会发生这样的事
I'd rather go to jail.
我宁愿进监狱。
I don't want to see it either
我也不想看到
Your current situation.
你现在的情况。
useless!
无用！
you are talking now
你现在正在说话
Are you still polite?
还有礼貌吗？
I do not care.
我不在乎。
I'm going to Guo'an tomorrow.
明天我要去国安。
to explain this.
来解释这一点。
nonsense.
废话。
I won't let you
我不会让你
Do whatever you want.
随心所欲。
Now, Zheng Guoxian
现在，郑国贤
Already assumed
已承担
Everything.
万物。
what do you want to do
你想让我做什么
I want everyone to try it
我想让每个人都尝试一下
Futile, right?
徒劳的，对吧？
Yeah.
呀呀。
When I was a child, my father told me
小时候，父亲告诉我
As a people we must prioritize honesty
作为一个人，我们必须优先考虑诚实
Trust should be a concern when doing something
做某事时应该关心信任
What are we doing now?
我们现在干什么？
not everything
不是所有的事情
as you think.
如你想象的。
He said he could release it immediately.
他说他可以立即释放它。
who are they?
他们是谁？
They are a spy organization.
他们是一个间谍组织。
They can kill you at any time.
他们随时都可以杀死你。
This is the Golden Sea, not the United States.
这里是金海，不是美国。
Because we fear him,
因为我们惧怕他，
Just caught by them
刚刚被他们抓住
then you say
然后你说
what should I do?
我应该怎么办？
Fang Yongping benar-benar
Fang Yongping benar-benar
Surrender for your son?
为了儿子投降？
We must stop him.
我们必须阻止他。
Can Chen Ting stabilize?
陈婷能否稳定下来？
very difficult.
非常困难。
What matters now is the square path.
现在重要的是方路。
surrender.
投降。
Yeah.
呀呀。
I can investigate.
我可以调查。
Orang Guo An
Orang Guo An
Definitely look into it.
绝对可以调查。
Sooner or later they will catch you.
迟早他们会抓住你的。
I already knew today was going to happen.
我已经知道今天会发生。
but i don't think so
但我不这么认为
You noticed it first.
你首先注意到了。
I will surrender.
我会投降。
But you must leave Jinhai first.
但你必须先离开金海。
Why?
为什么？
Because I am their target.
因为我是他们的目标。
they abuse you
他们虐待你
because I.
因为我。
You are innocent.
你是无辜的。
Sorry dad.
对不起爸爸。
I know it's hard to advise you to give up.
我知道很难建议你放弃。
But it's more difficult for me.
但这对我来说更困难。
Our family has reached the most difficult time
我们家已经到了最困难的时候
most needed
最需要的
have enough courage
有足够的勇气
Go face it.
去面对它。
And I am your child.
而我是你的孩子。
I can't leave you.
我不能离开你。
I hear you.
我听到你了。
but
但
Need to give me some more time.
需要再给我一些时间。
i must finish
我必须完成
solve something
解决一些事情
I certainly will
我一定会的
this matter.
这件事。
able
能
go back.
回去。
go to bed early.
早点休息。
I want to be alone
我想单独待一会儿
There was silence for a while.
沉默了一会儿。